manageengine.co.uk 2012-11-24

# ManageEngine Privacy Policy

| 

12th October 2006

[www.webnms.com](http://www.webnms.com/), [www.manageengine.com](http://www.manageengine.com/), [www.securecentral.com](http://www.securecentral.com/), [www.swissql.com](http://www.swissql.com/), [www.sqlone.com](http://www.sqlone.com/), [www.dbchangemanager.com](http://www.dbchangemanager.com/), [www.codeminer.com](http://www.codeminer.com/), [www.linuxmonitor.com](http://www.linuxmonitor.com/) and [www.zoho.com](http://www.zoho.com/) are websites owned by ZOHO Corp..

**Our postal address is**

ZOHO Corp.  
4900 Hopyard Rd., Suite 310   
Pleasanton, CA 94588, USA

We can be reached via e-mail at [support@manageengine.com](mailto:support@manageengine.com), or you can reach ManageEngine Customer Support Services by telephone at +1 925 924 9500 and +1-888-720-9500 (Monday to Friday). 

## General

You can visit most areas of our websites without providing personal information. But at times we do need such information for providing access to products or services requested by you. At ManageEngine we respect your need for online privacy and protect any information that you may share with us, in an appropriate manner. In compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, ManageEngine does not collect personal information from users who are under 13 years of age. By agreeing to use our products or services, you represent that you are 13 years or older.

## Information we collect

When you sign up for an ManageEngine service that requires registration or express interest in our products, we ask you for personal information such as your name and email address. You may also be asked to choose a unique username, a password, a security question and an answer to the security question. In addition, we collect information regarding the Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone and operating system of visitors to our websites. In case of products or services requiring payment, we request credit card or other payment account information, which will be used solely for processing payments. If you are a user of Zoho services, we also store and maintain your documents, to-do list and other data stored in your account in order to provide the services for which you are registered.

We use temporary and permanent cookies to enhance the experience on our websites. Temporary cookies will be removed from your computer each time you close your browser. By selecting ‘keep me signed-in’ option in Zoho services, a permanent cookie will be stored in your computer and you will not have to sign-in by providing complete login information, each time you return to our website. If you have turned cookies off, you may not be able to use registered areas of the websites.

## How we use Information

Your personal information such as name and email address is used to keep you informed on new products/versions/updates/service packs, upcoming events and changes in this privacy policy. Any alternate email address, security question and the answer to the security question, if given, will be used solely for the purpose of resetting password. We do not process or use the contents of your documents, to-do list and other data stored in Zoho accounts for any purpose other than to provide access to the services.

Your Financial Information will not be stored by us and will be used solely for processing payments. Subject to your prior consent and where necessary for processing future payments, your financial information will be stored in encrypted form on secure servers of reputed Payment Gateway Service Provider.

We use Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone and operating system of visitors collected in our log files to analyze the trends, administer the websites, track visitor's movements and to improve our applications.

Unless requested to the contrary by the customer, we publish the names of our customers other than individual users of Zoho services in the Customer List at our websites, press releases, advertisements, brochures and other promotional materials. 

We use cookies for easier access to our websites. Once you close your browser, the temporary cookies simply terminate, except for the permanent cookies created when you select the ‘keep me signed-in’ option.

## Links from our websites

Some pages of our websites contain external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such other websites. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide personal information, without assuring yourselves of the privacy policy of other websites. 

## With whom we share Information

We have partners/affiliates/resellers for specific products and services. We may share generic aggregated demographic information with our business partners/affiliates/ resellers and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. Your name and email address may occasionally be shared with our business partners/ affiliates/resellers in connection with our products/services and any use of your personal information by such business partners/ affiliates/resellers will be in accordance with this privacy policy. We do not share the contents of documents, to-do list and other data related to Zoho account maintained and stored by us with any third party.

## How secure is your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to \protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in your account. Access to your name and email address is restricted to our employees, contractors, business partners, affiliates and resellers who need to know such information in connection =with our products and services and are bound by confidentiality obligations.

## Your Choice in Information Use

You will be required to register for our services by providing personal information. You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case we may not be able to provide those services to you. While using our services, you are not allowed to opt out from receiving information on versions/updates/service packs. We will obtain your prior consent for use of your personal information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected or the purposes described in this privacy policy. In such cases we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of your personal information for those other purposes. 

## Accessing, Updating and Removing Personal Information 

Upon request we provide users with access to their personally identifiable information free of charge. Users may correct, update or remove any such personally identifiable information either through the users’ profile or by contacting ManageEngine Customer Support Services. Such changes may take up to 48 hours to take effect. 

## Enforcement of Privacy Policy

We make every effort including periodic reviews to ensure that personal information provided by you is used in conformity with this privacy policy. If you have any concerns regarding our adherence to this policy or the manner in which personal information is used on our websites, kindly contact ManageEngine Customer Support Services at [support@manageengine.com](mailto:support@manageengine.com). We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also co-operate with regulatory authorities in this regard.

## Notification of Changes 

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our websites in order to keep you informed of any changes in nature of information collected and manner of collection, use and sharing of information. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at <http://www.manageengine.com/privacy.html> periodically.

## END OF PRIVACY POLICY

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at [legal@manageengine.com](mailto:legal@manageengine.com)  
  
---|---
